我咧。
你。
pay for.
上年啊。
對。
係。
say there.
啊。
係專門做呢個事。
O.K.，多謝咁多位。
十咧就係畀一個實質辯論嘅。
當中咧就議案實質辯論嘅係八個半鐘頭，官員發言係一個半鐘頭，實際表決嘅時間咧係半個鐘頭。
嘅，噉我又有講講。誒喺十月廿五日開始，立法會照今日完成一地兩檢嘅審議咧，係用咗二十六小時。
啊！各位傳媒嘅朋友，首先咧，我係要感謝啊！咁多位議員咧，喺一個比較平靜嘅環境咧，係將一地兩檢咧得以表決。
亦都即係雖然係有火花咧，依個係議會嘅特色。啊，亦都明白到咧，議員係嘅睇法係南面北切嘅。咁但係都係一個相當平靜嘅啊環境係得以表決。噉我知道傳媒啊問我哋公共資訊部啊有啲數。
其餘嘅十五個半小時中咧，五個小時係用於點算法定人數，另外十個半小時係用於中止待續啊，要求新聞界同公眾人士離場啊等等，同埋一分鐘辯論等等嘅。咁實際大概係用咗四百分之四。
點睇咧？即係。
你所講嘅慣例，佢哋。
係，一啲品質。
揀咗意思來，因為過。
OK，唔該曬。
收緊，以及係即係發行經濟都係有擴失。
I think I have yet to receive.
Based on past experience, it will be a combined debate. That's from the past. What?
the request, the notice of the motion. So I think I need you know to study that at that time before I decide what to do.
Well, I think it. I just have to look at all the amendments and all the proposal before I decide on the timing and when and how long.
I would have to, I will decide. Will depends on what the members, you know, when they give notice, the amount and then the subject matter.
誒，我喺立法會咧，過去好多辯論咧都係用合拼辯論嘅，包括財政預算案都係一個合拼辯論嘅做法。咁所以，我哋都會係誒守住過往嘅做法咧，去處理誒將來佢哋會唔會提交依個辯論，噉我自決定。